

CONTACT

- jevinnaeuginian@gmail.com
- **** 08999653063
- Jalan SMEA VI No. 19 A Cawang, Kramat Jati

COMPUTER SKILLS

Microsoft Office:

- PowerPoint
- Excel
- Word
- in Jevinna Euginia Novianty

JEVINNA EUGINIA NOVIANTY

SECRETARY

ABOUT

A little bit about me, I was born at Jakarta 21 November 1999. I was graduated from Tarakanita Higher Educational Institution majoring in secretary with some internship also working experience. With an educational background secretarial study, I can handling filing, arrange schedule and taking minutes.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Tarakanita Higher Educational Institution -2017 SMAN 67 Halim Perdanakusuma - 2014

WORKING EXPERIENCES

SECRETARY

PT Rapid Infrastruktur Indonesia | November 2020 - Present

• Dealing with secretarial duties.

FINANCE

PT Rapid Infrastruktur Indonesia | August 2020 - November 2020

• Project Secretary.

ACCOUNTING (INTERNSHIP)

PT Berlian Laju Tanker | February 2020 - July 2020

Support accounting staff

FLEET ADMINISTRATION

Toyota Astra Finance Services | July 2018 - August 2018

• Handling banker clause project and insurance policies .

ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCES

- Chief of Student Senate 2018/2019
- Tarakanita Campus Ambassador 2018
- Chief of The Youth Comittee at GKP Ebenhaezer 2020/2022
- Secretary of The Youth Comittee at GKP Jakarta Region 2019/2021

PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENTS

- Self Development Seminar by Stellavingze International Indonesia
- Graphic Design by HIMDKV Binus
- Beauty Class by Catrice Cosmetics
- Table Manner by Aston Imperial Bekasi
- Presentation Skill by MarkPlus Institute